Finding Aid for Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (University of Michigan) Records, 1909-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Central Topical Files, 1929-2003
  - 1925-1989, 1975-circa 1985
    - Capital Outlay, 1975-1989; 3 folders (Box 69)
      [see also Boxes 94 and 140]
    - Capital Projects, 1977-1986; 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Care, 1974-1981 (Box 70)
    - Common Fund, 1975-1987 (Box 70)
    - Computing Center-Computer Purchase, 1972-1981 (Box 70)
    - Computing Center-Phototypesetter, 1983-1984 (Box 70)
    - Cook, Martha-Historical Information, 1925-1986 (Box 70)
    - Dearborn, University of Michigan, 1978-1987; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Development Office, 1981-1988; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Development and Communication, 1982-1987; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Development, Vice President for, 1988 (Box 70)
    - Energy Conservation, 1975-1986; 3 folders (Box 70)
    - Engineering-Capital Campaign, 1974-1984; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Flint-Riverfront, General, 1974-1985 (Box 71)
    - Gifts, 1976-1987; 3 folders (Box 71)
    - Gifts, Miscellaneous, 1973-1983 (Box 71)
    - Handicapped, 1974-1985 (Box 71)
    - Health Administration Press, 1984-1986 (Box 71)
    - Hospital
      - Budget and Reports to Regents on Financial Operations, 1981-1987; 2 folders (Box 71)
      - Medical Center, misc., 1985-1987; 6 folders (Box 71)
      - Replacement Financing, 1982-1987; 2 folders (Box 71)
      - Replacement Financing, State Building Authority [SBA] Lease and Bond Issue, 1982-1987; 3 folders (Box 72)
      - Revenue Refunding Bond Series A, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 72)
      - Revised Medicare Regulations, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 72)
      - Wayne County General Discussions, 1979-1984; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Housing, misc., 1983-1988; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Iowa, University of, Review of Vice President for Finance Office, 1985-1986 (Box 72)
    - ISDOS [Information Systems Design and Optimization System] Project, 1983-1987 (Box 72)
    - Labor Relations-AFSCME [American Federation of State and County Municipal Employees], 1973-1986; 4 folders (Box 72)
    - Labor Relations-AFSCME [American Federation of State and County Municipal Employees], 1973-1986; 1 folders (Box 76)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2016 ]
    - Labor Relations-Bogi, John, 1977-1984 (Box 76)
    - Labor Relations, misc., 1975-1985; 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Law School, 1983-1987
      - 1975-1978 (Box 73)
        (Souther gift)
      - S.K. Yee, 1977-1984 (Box 73)
    - Literature, Science and Arts, College of, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Management Incentives, 1984-1987 (Box 73)
    - Medical School Head Protection Program, 1980-1984 (Box 73)
    - Medical School Sports Medicine Program, 1980-1985 (Box 73)
    - Michigan Awareness Program, 1978-1986 (Box 73)
    - Michigan League, 1972-1979 (Box 73)
    - Michigan State Building Authority, 1976-1985; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Michigan, State of, 1983-1987 (Box 73)
    - Michigan, State of, Use and Finance Statements, 1974-1983 (Box 73)
    - Michigan Union, 1978-1981
      - Space, 1970-1980 (Box 73)
      - Term Loan, 1974 (Box 73)
    - NACUBO [National Association of College and University Business Officers], Large Institution Committee, 1986-1988; 4 folders (Box 73)
    - North Campus Planning Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 74)
    - Parke Davis, 1956-1980 (Box 74)
    - Parking, misc., 1974-1984; 3 folders (Box 74)
    - Parking Structure Fee Bonds, 1981 (Box 74)
    - Plant, misc., 1981-1984 (Box 74)
    - Professorships, 1969-1985 (Box 74)
    - Purchasing, misc., 1981-1989; 3 folders (Box 74)
    - Radrick Center, 1974-1985; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Research and Graduate Studies-Planning Committee on Merger, 1983-1984 (Box 74)
    - Research-Super Conducting Super-Collider, 1985-1989 (Box 74)
    - Research, misc., 1984-1987; 4 folders (Box 74)
    - Research, misc., 1988 (Box 75)
    - Safety, 1982-1987 (Box 75)
    - Security, 1981-1987 (Box 75)
    - Space Utilization, 1975-1986 (Box 75)
    - Staff Benefits
      - Group Life Insurance, 1971-1981 (Box 75)
      - Retirement (TIAA/CREF), 1973-1983 (Box 75)
        [see also Boxes 137 and 142]
      - Social Security, 1964-1980 (Box 75)
    - Student Aid
      - Gerald R. Ford Scholarship, 1981-1982 (Box 75)
      - Scholarships, Loans, etc., 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Student Publication, Board for, 1976-1985
      - Financial Statements, 1976-1985 (Box 75)
    - Surveys of University Policies, 1985-1986 (Box 75)
    - Telecommunications Planning, 1981-1984; 2 folders
      - Office of Administrative Systems, 1980-1982 (Box 75)
      - UMNet, 1979-1982 (Box 75)
    - Transportation, 1981-1985 (Box 75)
    - University Club, 1973-1989 (Box 75)
    - University Press, 1983-1986
      - Financial Statements, 1983-1985 (Box 75)
      - Report to Dean Sussman, 1985 (Box 75)
    - Urban Area Transportation Study, 1978-1980 (Box 75)
    - Utilities, 1977-1987 (Box 75)
  - 1937-1999, 1980-1991
    The 1937-1999 topical files, accessioned in 2000, is largest to date from the Office of Vice President and Chief Financial Officer. The transfer consists of 55 linear feet of alphabetically arranged Topical Files spanning the period from 1937 to 1999. The bulk of the documentation, however, falls within the years 1980-1991. The records are largely in the order and condition in which they were received, maintaining the filing conventions and terminology utilized by the office. In some cases, topics will have numerous subdivisions within the hierarchical structure. Overall, the records illuminate the university's fiscal policies, investments, properties, and policies, as well as campus-wide topics such as affirmative action, labor relations, and staff benefits.
    - Administrative Systems, 1984-1989 (Box 85)
    - Affirmative Action
      - Miscellaneous, 1981-1991 (Box 85)
      - Business Office Staff, 1980-1990 (Box 85)
      - Diversity and Racism, 1986-1991 (Box 85)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 85)
      - Minorities, 1986-1991 (Box 85)
      - Women (Communication, etc.), 1974-1991 (Box 85)
    - Alcohol and Other Drugs, Task Force On, 1990-1991 (Box 85)
    - Alumni Association (Box 86)
      - Historical Information, 1946-1977 (Box 86)
      - General, 1983-1987 (Box 86)
      - Budget and Finance, 1987-1991 (Box 86)
    - Alumni Center Project
      - Letters Regarding Alumni Building (Box 86)
    - Ann Arbor School Board, 1971-1991
      - Conveyance of North Campus Land to Ann Arbor School Board for Huron High School (Box 86)
    - Ann Arbor/University Relations, 1985-1991; 3 folders (Box 86)
    - Ann Arbor/University Ad Hoc Strategic Alternatives Task Force (Box 86)
    - Arborcrest Cemetery, 1975-1981 (Box 86)
    - Astronomy
      - Lamont-Hussey Observatory (South Africa), 1937-1975 (Box 86)
      - Observatory-Peach Mountain, 1950-1978 (Box 86)
      - Relocation of Telescope to Kitt Peak, 1974-1975 (Box 86)
    - Athletics (Box 87)
      - General, 1980-1991; 3 folders (Box 87)
      - American Football Coaches Retirement Trust (Box 87)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics, Board In Control of
        - General, 1989-1991; 3 folders (Box 87)
        - Finance Committee Meeting, March 20, 1991 (Box 87)
        - January 30, 1990 (Box 87)
      - Financial, 1974-1986
        - Budgets And Expenses, 1979-1986 (Box 87)
    - Audit (Box 88)
      - Auditor General
        - Dearborn, 1975-1980 (Box 88)
        - Flint, 1975-1980 (Box 88)
      - General Fund, 1980-1981
        - State Audit Report Materials (Box 88)
        - Auditor General Report Materials (Box 88)
      - Plant and Construction (Box 88)
      - HEW, 1975-1982 (Box 88)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-1991; 2 folders (Box 89)
      - Outside Auditors, 1978; 1991; 4 folders (Box 89)
      - Outside Checking Accounts (Internal Medical Trust), 1986-1991 (Box 89)
      - Reports to Regents, 1987-1991 (Box 89)
      - Sales Tax, 1972-1988 (Box 89)
    - Banks, Miscellaneous, 1965-1991 (Box 89)
    - Big Ten (Box 90)
      - Financial Officers Subcommittee On Revenue Sharing, 1989-1992; 3 folders; 3 hanging files (Box 90)
      - Financial Officers Subcommittee On Revenue Sharing, 1993-1994; 3 hanging files (Box 91)
      - Big Ten Business Officers Meetings
        - University of Michigan, November 18-20, 1984 (Box 91)
        - Miscellaneous, 1983-1991; 2 folders (Box 91)
    - Biological Station, 1984-1991
      - Colonial Point Forest (Box 91)
      - Verdor Property (Box 91)
    - Broadcasting And Media Service, 1988-1991 (Box 91)
    - Budget (Box 92)
      - Committee On Budget Administration (CBA), 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Reports For Publications (Record, Etc.), 1976-1991; 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Year-End (Closing And Fiscal Reports), 1985-1991 (Box 92)
    - Business and Finance (Box 93)
      - Goals and Objectives, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Seminars, 1988-1991; 4 folders (Box 93)
    - Business Administration, 1986-1991 (Box 94)
    - Business School Growth Fund, 1986-1991 (Box 94)
    - Camps, Miscellaneous, 1967-1991 (Box 94)
    - Campus Planning, 1979-1991 (Box 94)
    - Canham, Donald Trust (Box 94)
    - Capital Outlay, Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 94)
      [see also Boxes 69 and 140]
    - Capital Projects, 1987-1991 (Box 94)
    - Central Campus Plan Study, 1962-1963 (Box 94)
    - Central Campus Planning Study, 1976 (Box 94)
    - Commencement (President Bush Visit), May 4, 1991; 2 folders (Box 94)
    - Common Fund History (Beginning)., 1969-1970 (Box 95)
    - Communications, Director Of, 1988-1991 (Box 95)
    - Community Relation, 1991 (Box 95)
    - Compensation
      [see also Box 141]
      - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 95)
      - Administrative Salaries, 1984-1991; 2 folders (Box 95)
      - Salary Disclosure (Box 95)
      - Salary Equity Study, 1988-1990 (Box 95)
      - Salary Increase Program
        - 1982-1986 (Box 95)
        - 1988-1991, 2 folders (Box 96)
      - Salary Studies, Miscellaneous, 1987-1991 (Box 96)
    - Competition-Public/Private, 1985-1991 (Box 96)
    - Computers And Networking, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Computers, UM Personal Sales, 1983-1991; 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1970-1991; 3 folders (Box 97)
    - Construction-Costs, etc. (Management Process, Bidding Procedures, Complaints and Responses), 1973-1988 (Box 97)
    - Consultants, Miscellaneous, 1977-1991 (Box 97)
    - Cook Trust, W. W., 1961-1989 (Box 97)
    - Dearborn U of M, 1988-1991 (Box 97)
    - Dearborn-Fairlane, 1974-1991 (Box 97)
    - Dearborn-Parking Program, 1974-1987 (Box 97)
    - Delegation of Authority, 1968-1991; 3 folders (Box 98)
    - Dental School, 1985-1991 (Box 98)
    - Detroit Edison, 1974-1989 (Box 98)
    - Development
      - Development Office, 1988-1991 (Box 98)
      - Development and Univ. Relations Vice President Search (Box 98)
      - New Capital Campaign
        - Campaign Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 98)
        - Campaign Operating Group, 1990 (Box 98)
        - Campaign Steering Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 98)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 99)
        - President's Advisory Group, 1990-1991 (Box 99)
      - Policy Committee, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 99)
      - Development, Vice President for, 1990 (Box 99)
      - Advisory Group, November 3, 1989; 2 folders (Box 99)
      - Campaign Planning Advisory Group, June 20, 1989 (Box 99)
    - Disabilities Information, 1986-1991 (Box 99)
    - Diversity, Business, and Finance, 1989-1991 (Box 100)
    - Dow Foundation and Dow Chemical, 1980-1991 (Box 100)
    - Education, School of, 1979-1991; 2 folders (Box 100)
    - Energy Conservation, 1987-1991 (Box 100)
    - Engineering, College of, 1985-1991 (Box 100)
    - Engineering Society of Detroit Parking at Rackham, 1972-1978 (Box 100)
      (except 1977)
    - Environmental Task Force, 1989-1990 (Box 100)
    - Equipment Historic-Preservation, 1985-1986 (Box 100)
    - Estates
      - McKay, 1957-1991 (Box 100)
      - Thurnau Charitable Trust (Box 101)
        - 1979-1983 (Box 101)
        - 1984-1991 (Box 101)
      - Weber, Helen F.
        - Weber Estate, 1975-1977 (Box 101)
        - Weber Estate Lowmoor Lake Property, 1977 (Box 101)
        - Weber Estate-Mining Lease, 1978 (Box 101)
        - Weber Request of, 1975-1976 (Box 101)
        - Miscellaneous, 1978-1980; 1986-1988 (Box 101)
    - Fees
      - Fees and Tuition, 1986-1991 (Box 101)
      - Income, 1978-1984 (Box 101)
      - Information, 1963-1991 (Box 101)
    - Finances
      - Financial Operations, Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 101)
      - Financial Report, 1975-1991 (Box 101)
      - Financing Internal Loans, 1969-1988 (Box 101)
    - Flint-U of M
      - Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 101)
      - Flint-Capital Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 101)
      - Search for Chancellor, 1984 (Box 102)
      - Miscellaneous, 1959-1961; 1982-1987 (Box 102)
    - Ford, Gerald R.
      - Ford Foundation Endowment For Library, 1986-1990 (Box 102)
      - Gerald R. Ford Fellowships, 1987-1988 (Box 102)
    - Foundations, 1984-1991 (Box 102)
    - Fund Raising, 1984-1991 (Box 102)
    - Gifts
      - Buildings, 1965-1978 (Box 102)
      - Current, 1988-1991 (Box 102)
      - Pooled Life Income NBD as Trustee 1974 (Donor Pooled), 1977-1991, 1974-1991 (Box 102)
      - Receiving, Miscellaneous, 1983-1989 (Box 102)
      - Receiving Policies and Procedures, 1977-1991 (Box 102)
      - Reports, 1978-1991 (Box 102)
      - Undesignated Requests
        - 1967-1976 (Box 102)
        - 1977-1991 (Box 103)
    - Health Service, 1983-1991; 2 folders (Box 103)
    - Higher Education
      - Center for Higher Education Finance Seminar, 1985-1991; 3 folders (Box 103)
      - Task Force on Costs., 1989-1991 (Box 103)
      - Miscellaneous, 1978-1986 (Box 103)
    - Hospital
      - Accounts Receivable, Payable, Audit, Etc., 1977-1989 (Box 103)
      - Ambulance SVC 1981-1987 (except 1982 and 1984) (Box 103)
      - Budget and Reports to Regents on Financial, Operations, 1989-1991 (Box 104)
      - Capital Planning, 1985-1991 (Box 104)
      - Chelsea Medical Center, 1977-1991 (Box 104)
      - Financial Statements, 1988-1991 (Box 104)
      - Health Maintenance Or.(M-Care), 1989-1991 (Box 104)
      - Health Maintenance Organization (M-Care), 1986-1991; 3 folders (Box 104)
      - Medical Center
        - Parking, 1985-1986 (Box 104)
        - Planning, 1974-1990 (Box 105)
        - Miscellaneous, 1989-1991; 2 folders (Box 105)
      - Nurses, 1978-1983 (Box 105)
      - Organization, 1978-1989 (Box 105)
      - Personnel, 1982-1991; 2 folders (Box 105)
      - Personnel Task Team, 1977-1984 (Box 105)
      - Replacement (Box 106)
        - Capital Campaign-Taubman, 1980-1985; 1988-1990 (Box 106)
        - Fate Of Old Main, 1984-1989; 2 folders (Box 106)
        - Lawsuits, 1983-1986 (Box 106)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1991; 3 folders (Box 106)
    - Housing
      - Historical Information, 1979 (Box 107)
      - Residence Hall Rate, 1980-1991 (Box 107)
      - Task Force on Faculty, Staff and Student Housing, 1988-1991 (Box 107)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 107)
    - Hughes Medical Institute, 1988-1991
      - HHMI Billing, 1984-1991; 2 folders (Box 107)
      - Miscellaneous, 1984-1991; 2 folders (Box 107)
    - Indirect Costs
      - Glen Hearing on NSF Grants, Washington, D.C., September 1991 (Box 107)
      - HHS (Healy) Study (November 1991) and FWW Analysis (1992) (Box 107)
      - Materials For Press Conference, September 11, 1991 (Box 108)
      - Meetings
        - AAU/Danforth IDC Meeting St. Louis, Missouri, November 19-20, 1991 (Box 108)
        - Capitol Hill Meetings, May 28-29, 1991 (Box 108)
        - OMB and OSTP Meeting, September 21, 1991 (Box 108)
        - Rep. John Dingell Meeting, July 22, 1991 (Box 108)
      - Records
        - 1987-1989 (Box 108)
        - March-December, 1990 (Box 108)
        - January, 1991 (Box 108)
        - March-July, 1991, 5 folders (Box 108)
        - August-December, 1991, 6 folders (Box 109)
    - Industrial Technology Institute (ITI)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 109)
      - undated (Box 109)
    - Information Technology
      - Executive Computer Committee, 1989-1991; 3 folders (Box 109)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-1991; 4 folders (Box 110)
    - Inglis House, 1977-1991 (Box 110)
    - Institute for Social Research (ISR), 1959-1991; 2 folders (Box 110)
    - Insurance
      - Miscellaneous, 1986-1991 (Box 110)
      - Michigan Business Officers Liability Insurance Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 111)
      - Listening Post Group (NELM)
        - Helm Insurance Meeting, Chicago, IL, July 1, 1987 (Box 111)
        - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box 111)
      - Nacubo Insurance Group (SCUUL), 1986 (Box 111)
      - Veritas Insurance Corporation [see also Box 141]
        - Records, 1990-1991; 3 folders (Box 111)
        - Board of Directors Meetings and Correspondence, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 112)
    - Intellectual Properties
      - 1982-1986, 3 folders (Box 112)
      - 1987-1991, 2 folders (Box 113)
    - Investments
      - Construction Projects-Student Fee, 1986-1987 (Box 113)
      - Contacts, 1989-1991 (Box 113)
      - Endowment Performance, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 113)
      - Managers
        - 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box 113)
        - 1991 (Box 114)
      - Mortgages, 1972-1991; 2 folders (Box 114)
      - Office Miscellaneous, 1985-1991; 3 folders (Box 114)
      - Oil and Mineral Rights in, 1973-1991; 2 folders (Box 114)
      - Options, 1987 (Box 114)
      - Parking System Revenue Bonds, 1986-1988 (Box 115)
      - Policies, and Procedures, 1968-1991; 2 folders (Box 115)
      - Purchase of Eisenhour Construction Co. Stock, 1980-1985 (Box 115)
      - Rating Agencies, 1990-1991 (Box 115)
      - Reports to Regents
        - 1980-1986, 5 folders (Box 115)
        - 1986-1990, 6 folders (Box 116)
        - 1991 (Box 117)
      - Retreats, 1989 (Box 117)
      - South Africa Investments, 1977-1979; 1985-1986; 1988; 1993; 1998 (Box 117)
      - Trust Funds, 1978-1991; 4 folders (Box 117)
    - Judaic Studies Program, 1988-1991 (Box 117)
    - Kellogg Foundation, 1966-1990; 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Kelsey Museum, 1986-1987 (Box 118)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1974-1991 (Box 118)
    - Labor Contracts, 1972-1991 (Box 118)
    - Labor Relations
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1991; 2 folders (Box 118)
      - ASFCME, 1987-1991; 2 folders (Box 118)
      - Building and Trades, 1974-1991; 2 folders (Box 118)
      - Clerical/Secretaries
        - 1974-1982, 2 folders (Box 118)
        - 1983-1991 (Box 119)
      - Faculty, 1975-1983 (Box 119)
      - Grad Students-GEO-, 1975-1986; 4 folders (Box 119)
      - Interns and Residents, 1971-1989 (Box 119)
      - Nurses, 1967-1991; 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Law School, 1989-1991 (Box 119)
    - Legal
      - Miscellaneous, 1984-1991; 2 folders (Box 119)
      - Defense and Indemnification Cases, 1990-1991 (Box 119)
      - Fees, 1971-1991 (Box 119)
      - Lawsuits, 1973-1991; 4 folders (Box 120)
      - Legal Opinions, 1973-1991; 3 folders (Box 120)
      - Legal Trademark Program, 1978-1991 (Box 120)
      - Library, 1984-1991 (Box 120)
      - Likert, Rensis Assoc., 1973-1983 (Box 120)
      - Liquor Licenses, 1983-1991 (Box 120)
    - LS and A, College of, 1988-1991 (Box 120)
    - M-Quality
      - Records, 1990-1992; 8 folders (Box 121)
    - M-Quality, 1993-1999; 9 folders (Box 122)
    - M, Miscellaneous, 1987-1991 (Box 123)
    - McKinley Associates, Inc., Edison Institute, 1990 (Box 123)
    - Medical Affairs
      - Vice Provost for Medical Affairs, 1983-1991 (Box 123)
      - Vice Provost Search, 1983 (Box 123)
    - Medical School
      - General Information, 1990-1991 (Box 123)
      - Affiliations, 1984-1988 (Box 123)
      - Johnson and Johnson Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 123)
      - Medical School E.O. Retreat, June 11, 1990 (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 123)
      - Separate Legal Entities, 1983-1989; 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Memberships, 1980-1991; 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Michigan Bell, 1976-1986 (Box 124)
    - Michigan College and Business Officers (MCUBO)
      - Officers Meetings, 1989-1992; 5 folders (Box 124)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1992 (Box 124)
    - Michigan Council of State Colleges Presidents (MCSCP), 1989-1991 (Box 124)
    - Michigan Daily, 1966-1990 (Box 124)
    - Michigan League
      - Miscellaneous, 1966-1991; 2 folders (Box 124)
      - Historical Documents 1927, 1930, 1962-1963, 1966-1969 (except 1967), 1927-1969 (Box 124)
    - Michigan Mandate, 1988-1991 (Box 124)
    - Michigan, State of
      - Budget, 1989-1991 (Box 125)
      - Building Authority, 1982-1991 (Box 125)
      - Legislative Bills, 1971-1991; 4 folders (Box 125)
      - Materials for Meeting with Bowman, October 13, 1988 (Box 125)
      - Meeting with Bob Bowman, JJD, BLK Lansing, Michigan, 1988 (Box 125)
      - Michigan Appropriations, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 125)
      - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 125)
      - Prepaid Tuition Plan
        - 1986-1991, 4 folders (Box 126)
        - Miscellaneous, 1987; 1991 (Box 126)
        - Use and Financial Statements, 1985-1991 (Box 126)
    - Michigan Student Assembly (Box 126)
    - Michigan Union
      - History, 1950; 1968-1969; 1972-1973; 1976 (Box 126)
      - Miscellaneous 1969-1991 (except 1979-1981), 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Museum of Art, 1962-1991 (Box 126)
    - Music, School of, 1985-1989
      - Capital Campaign, 1980-1985 (Box 126)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1985; 1988-1989 (Box 126)
    - Music Society, 1982-1991 (Box 126)
    - NACUBO-Large Institutions Committee, 1989-1990
      - Correspondence
        - Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 127)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 127)
      - Proactive Chief Business Office-Partner in Medical Center, 1989 (Box 127)
    - Names (Streets and Buildings), 1963-1990 (Box 127)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1977-1991 (Box 127)
    - Organization
      - Department Personnel
        - General, 1987-1991 (Box 127)
        - Organization Charts, 1977-1991 (Box 127)
      - VP/CFO
        - Department, and Staff Development, 1971-1988 (Box 127)
        - Personnel, 1968-1986 (Box 127)
      - University, 1973-1991 (Box 127)
    - P, Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 128)
    - Parking
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-1991; 4 folders (Box 128)
      - Central Campus Parking Study
        - General, 1988-1990 (Box 128)
        - Study Books, 1988-1989 (Box 128)
      - VIP Parking Permits, 1984-1987; 1989-1991; 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Patents and Copyrights, 1961; 1968; 1977-1979; 1980; 1984-1985 (Box 128)
    - Payroll, 1968-1991 (Box 129)
    - Personnel
      - Miscellaneous, 1982-1991; 3 folders (Box 129)
      - Operational Review of Department, 1978-1981 (Box 129)
      - Reclassifications, 1978-1990 (Box 129)
      - Reduction in Force (RIF) Information, 1977-1982 (Box 129)
      - Search for New Director, 1978 (Box 129)
      - Training and Development, 1975-1991 (Box 129)
    - Pharmacy, College of, 1976-1991; 2 folders (Box 129)
    - PEW Higher Education Roundtable, 1994-1995 (Box 130)
    - Plant, Miscellaneous, 1985-1991 (Box 130)
    - Plant Extension Committee Meetings, 1977-1987; 3 folders (Box 130)
    - Plant Operations/ Plant Extension Review, 1981-1987 (Box 130)
    - Policies and Procedures
      - Policy for University Archives and Records, 1991 (Box 130)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1970-1987, 4 folders (Box 130)
        - 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box 131)
    - Power, Eugene B. (Regent Emeritus)
      - 1963-1974 (Box 131)
      - 1981-1991 (Box 131)
    - Presidents Club, 1987-1990 (Box 131)
    - Prismatic Club, 1967; 1978-1980; 1985-1987 (Box 131)
    - Purchasing
      - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 131)
      - Reports to Regents, 1988-1991 (Box 131)